let quiz=[
    {
        question:"react is a ?",
        option:[
            "javascript library",
            "framework",
            "both of the above",
            "none of the above",
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:" react js covers covers_____",
        option:[
            "User Interface layer in an application",
            "Data layer in an appliaction",
            "both of the above",
            " none of the above",
            
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"AngularJs directives are used in",
        option:[
            "Module",
            "Controller",
            "Service",
            "View",   
        ],
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        question:"which file is responsible for startup of angular2 project ?",
        option:[
            "main.ts",
            "index.js",
            "app.ts",
            "angular.cli.json",   
        ],
        answer:1,

    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following class is required to be added to form tag to make it horizontal?",
        option:[
            ".horizontal",
            ".form-horizontal",
            ".horizontal",
            "none of the above",   
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"which of the following bootstrap style is used for a basic button group?",
        option:[
            ".btn-group",
            ".btn-toolbar",
            ".btn-group-lg",
            ".btn-group-vertical",   
        ],
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question:"Which directive initializes an angular js application?",
        option:[
            "ng-init",
            "ng-app",
            "ngsrc",
            "ng-start",   
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following will return the type of the arguments passed to a function ?",
        option:[
            "using getType function",
            "using typeof operator",
            "Both of the above",
            "None",   
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"AngularJs expressions are written using",
        option:[
            "(expression)",
            "{{expression}}",
            "{{{expression}}}",
            "[expression]",   
        ],
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Angular is based on ",
        option:[
            "MVC architecture",
            "Decorator pattern",
            "MVVM architectural pattern",
            "observer pattern",   
        ],
        answer:3,
    }
]